David Kiefer Theatre Collection 118
People's Archive, MLK Library
David Kiefer Theatre Collection
1903-200
1952-1994
People's Archive, MLK Library
Kiefer, David
118
2 Boxes
Arrangement
Series 1: Performance programs The series contains performance programs and playbills from various Washington, D.C. theatres. Some are notable venues like the Source Theatre and Kennedy Center; others are small and less prominent. Series 2: Theatre seasons The series contains seasonal programs detailing a particular theatre's schedule of shows and highlighted performances. Series 3: Printed material This series contains theatre publications, newsletters, and clippings from Washington, D.C. newspapers on issues related to the theatre community. It is divided into four sub-series: 1. Publications, 2. Newsletters, 3. Clippings, and 4. Press releases. Sub-series 1: Publications This sub-series contains publications, such as magazines, by local theatres. Sub-series 2: Newsletters This sub-series contains newsletters published by local theatres. Sub-series 3: Clippings This sub-series contains clippings from D.C. newspapers on issues related to the theatre community. Sub-series 4: Press releases This sub-series contains press releases related to the theatre community. Series 4: Miscellaneous This series contains advertisement campaigns, jazz event advertisements, newsletters, performance flyers, publications, and theatre calendars, surveys, and questionnaires.
Biographical / Historical
The theatre community has been a rich contributor to the cultural and social life of Washington, D.C. since the beginning of the city's history. This collection of theatre programs and other related materials belonged to David Kiefer, a local Washington, D.C.-area resident and avid theatre buff.
Custodial History
David Kiefer donated this collection to the DC Public Library in 2008.
Scope and Contents
This collection consists of newsletters, programs, publications, and other materials related to Washington, D.C. theatres.
Performing Arts; Programs; Theatres; Ephemera
- Series 1:Performance Programs
  - American Playwright Theatre, Undated (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - American Theatre, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Arena Stage, 1952-1957 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Arena State, 1965-1966 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Arena Stage, 1970-1976 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Arena Stage, 1977-1979 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Arena Stage, 1980-1981 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Arena Stage, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Arena Stage, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Arena Stage (Folder 1 of 2), 1984 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Arena Stage (Folder 2 of 2), 1984 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Arena Stage (Folder 1 of 2), 1985 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Arena Stage (Folder 2 of 2), 1985 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Arena Stage (Folder 1 of 2), 1986 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Arena Stage (Folder 2 of 2), 1986 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Arena Stage, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Arena Stage, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Arena Stage, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Arena Stage, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Arena Stage, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Arena Stage, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Arena Stage, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Arena Stage, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Arena Stage, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Arena Stage, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Arena Stage, 1997-1998 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Carter Barron Amphitheatre, 1952-1954 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Carter Barron Amphitheatre, 1955-1969 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Catholic University of America (University Theatre), 1955 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Constitution Hall, 1952-1954 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Folger Theatre, 1979-1981 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Folger Theatre, 1982-1989 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Ford's Theatre, 1974-1990 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Ford's Theatre, 1990-1994 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Horizons Theatre, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Kennedy Center for Performing Arts, 1972-1973 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Kennedy Center for Performing Arts, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Kennedy Center for Performing Arts, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Kennedy Center for Performing Arts, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Kennedy Center for Performing Arts, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Kennedy Center for Performing Arts, 1978-1979 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Kennedy Center for Performing Arts, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Kennedy Center for Performing Arts, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Kennedy Center for Performing Arts, 1982-1983 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Kennedy Center for Performing Arts, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Kennedy Center for Performing Arts, 1985 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Kennedy Center for Performing Arts, 1986 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Kennedy Center for Performing Arts, 1987 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Kennedy Center for Performing Arts, 1988-1989 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Kennedy Center for Performing Arts, 1990-1991 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Kennedy Center for Performing Arts, 1992-1993 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Kennedy Center for Performing Arts, 1994-1995 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Kennedy Center for Performing Arts, 1996 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Kennedy Center for Performing Arts, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Kennedy Center for Performing Arts, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Kennedy Center for Performing Arts, 1999 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Loews Capitol Theatre, 1955 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - National Theatre, 1952-1953 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - National Theatre, 1954 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - New National Theatre, 1903-1921 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - National Theatre, 1955 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - National Theatre, 1956-1957 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - National Theatre, 1960-1961 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - National Theatre, 1962-1963 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - National Theatre, 1964-1965 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - National Theatre, 1966-1967 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - National Theatre, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - National Theatre, 1969-1972 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - National Theatre, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - National Theatre, 1976-1977 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - National Theatre, 1984-1986 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - National Theatre, 1988-1989 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - National Theatre, 1992-1998 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - National Theatre, Undated (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - New Playwrights Theatre, Undated (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Samuel Shubert Theatre, 1952-1957 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Shady Grove Music Fair, 1966 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Shakespeare Theatre, 1993-1999 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Source Theatre, 1986-1998 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Source Theatre, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Trinity Theatre, 1964 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Washington Performing Arts Society, 1966 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Washington Stage Guild, 1989-1999 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Washington Theater Club, 1963-1971 (Box 6, Folder 11)
- Series 2: Theatre Seasons
  - American Playwrights Theatre, 1989 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Arena Stage, 1961-1967 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Arena Stage, 1968-1973 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Arena Stage, 1982-1983 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Arena Stage, 1985-1999 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Catholic University of America, Undated (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Kennedy Center for Performing Arts, 1995-1999 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - New Playwrights' Theatre, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Shakespeare Theatre, 1981-1987 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Shakespeare Theatre, 1989-1992 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Shakespeare Theatre, 1992-1993 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Shakespeare Theatre, 1993-1994 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Shakespeare Theatre, 1994-1995 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Shakespeare Theatre, 1995-1996 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Shakespeare Theatre, 1996-1997 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Shakespeare Theatre, 1997-1998 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Shakespeare Theatre, 1998-1999 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Shakespeare Theatre, 1999-2000 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Source Theatre, 1993-1994 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Studio Theatre, 1986-1987 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Washington Stage Guild, 1989-1997 (Box 8, Folder 6)
- Series 3: Printed Material
  - Subseries 1: Publications
    - Arena Stage (America's Arena), 1982-1987 (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Arena Stage (On Stage at Arena Stage), 1990-1993 (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Filene Center (Performer Magazine), 1971 (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Ford's Theatre (Performer Magazine), 1971-1972 (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Georgetown Theatre (Georgetown Theatre News), 1952-1954 (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - Kennedy Center for Performing Arts (Opera House), 1971-1972 (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - National Theatre (Onstage Magazine), 1973 (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - Shakespeare Theatre (Asides), 1989 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Theatre unknown (Blacksgage Magazine), 1973 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Subseries 2: Newsletters
    - Ford's Theatre (Ford's Footnotes), 1975 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - New Playwrights' Theatre (New Playwrights'), 1975 (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Source Theatre (Source Theatre Company News), 1989 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Subseries 3: Clippings
    - President Ronald Reagan Booed at Kennedy Center, Undated (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - Robert Joffrey Ballet, 1982 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Subseries 4: Press Releases
    - Washington Theater Club, Undated (Box 9, Folder 8)
- Series 4: Miscellaneous
  - Advertisement campaigns, Undated (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Jazz event advertisements, 1956, 1963 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Performance flyers, 1977-1979 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Performance programs, 1953-1970 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Publications, 1977-1991 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - "Sweet Honey in the Rock" concert, 1985 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Theatre calendars, Undated (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Theatre surveys and questionnaires, Undated (Box 9, Folder 16)